

KASPER ALBERS

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

KASPERALBERS@GMAIL.COM +32 470 55 10 03





PROFILE

Generalist. Entrepreneurial mind. Polyglot.

Experience in sales and business development before enrolling in a coding bootcamp at Le Wagon Berlin to develop technical skills. I am now looking forward to continuing my professional journey in the field of web development.

EDUCATION

Full-stack web development | Apr - Jun 2022

Le Wagon Berlin Coding Bootcamp - Batch #870

- · 9-week full-time coding bootcamp
- Project lead for Careview: a web app that helps you find a carehome (two-week sprint)

EIT Climate-KIC Journey | Jul - Aug 2020

European Institute of Innovation and Technology

• Europe's biggest climate innovation summer school

Master in Business Administration | 2018 - 2019

Koninklijke Universiteit Leuven

- Strategy, Innovation, and Entrepreneurship
- Master's thesis: How to reduce CO2 emissions from cars?

Erasmus exchange | 2018

Université de Montpellier

Bachelor of Applied Economics | 2015 - 2018

Solvay Business School (Brussels)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap JavaScript ES6 Ruby on Rails Relational databases, SQL, PostgreSQL Wireframes, Prototyping, UI Design, Figma

WORK EXPERIENCE

Key account manager | Jan 2021 - Mar 2022

Too Good To Go (Belgium)

· Successfully managed key chains from lead generation to rollout (e.g. AB Inbev, Sodexo, Gorillas,...)

Business developer | Aug 2019 - Dec 2020

Too Good To Go (Belgium)

- Onboarded > 300 food stores
- Led rollout of CRM (Salesforce)

Volunteer | Mar 2020 - May 2020

HEROmeals (Belgium)

- · Free meals for medical staff during Covidcrisis
- · Scaled operations to Brussels

LANGUAGES

Dutch - native C2

Enalish - fluent C1

French - fluent C1

Spanish - work in progress B1

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Books: son of a writer and an illustrator Food: aspiring plant based master chef Photography: street and portrait Sports: from football to chess to surfing Startups and entrepreneurship